<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022 AM2R Community Developers -->
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>io.github.am2rcommunitydevelopers.AM2RLauncher</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
    <name>AM2RLauncher</name>
    <developer_name>AM2R Community Developers</developer_name>
    <summary>A front-end for dealing with AM2R updates and mods</summary>
    <categories>
        <category>Game</category>
    </categories>
    <description>
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake) is a fan-made remake of <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> in the style of <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em>.
            It was released in 2016 by DoctorM64 and his team, and very soon after, has received a DMCA letter from Nintendo.<br>
            A few years after, multiple members of the community managed to reverse engineer the game and published unofficial updates, 
            dubbed the AM2R-Community-Updates. Those fixed bugs and added new features like widescreen, added content planned by the original devs before 
            they were struck down, and ported it to other platforms.  
        </p>
        <p>
            The AM2RLauncher lets you conveniently play those Community-Updates, automatically receive updates, install AM2R mods and create 
            APKs to play on your phone.<br>
            No copyrighted files are shipped, you need to provide your own copy of AM2R_11!
        </p>
        <p>
            For further questions regarding AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">see this FAQ</a>.
            For further questions regarding the AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">see this Wiki</a>.
            For further communication, you can reach us on <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, 
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, or 
            <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub issues</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="es"> 
        <p>
            AM2R (<em>Another Metroid 2 Remake</em>, que significa Otro Remake de Metroid 2) es un remake del juego para la Game Boy 
            <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> hecho por fans, utilizando un estilo similar al de <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em> para Game Boy Advance. 
            Lanzado originalmente en 2016 por DoctorM64 y su equipo, al poco tiempo recibió un aviso por parte de Nintendo, indicando que infringía 
            la Ley de Derechos de Autor de la Era Digital.<br>
            Unos años más tarde, un grupo de miembros pertenecientes a la comunidad lograron reproducir el funcionamiento del juego mediante ingeniería inversa 
            y consiguieron publicar actualizaciones no oficiales, apodadas <em>AM2R-Community-Updates</em> (Actualizaciones de la Comunidad de AM2R). 
            Estas actualizaciones arreglaron algunos bugs y añadieron características nuevas como la posibilidad de jugar en pantalla ancha, 
            así como otros contenidos extra que los desarrolladores originales tenían planeado lanzar antes de que les cerraran el proyecto. 
            También han conseguido portear el juego a otros sistemas.
        </p>
        <p>
            El programa AM2RLauncher te permite jugar de forma fácil a esas Actualizaciones de la Comunidad, recibir actualizaciones automáticas, 
            instalar mods para AM2R y crear archivos APK para poder jugar en tu móvil.<br>
            ¡No contiene ningún archivo protegido con copyright, deberás proporcionar tu propia copia de AM2R_11!
        </p>
        <p>
            Para más preguntas sobre AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">visita este FAQ</a>.
            Para más preguntas sobre AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">visita esta Wiki</a>.
            Para hablar con nosotros, puedes contactar mediante <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, 
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, o <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.am2rcommunitydevelopers.AM2RLauncher.desktop</launchable>
    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues</url>
    <url type="faq">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki/FAQ</url>
    <url type="help">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki</url>
    <releases>
        <release version="2.2.0" date="2022-01-07"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="language-humor">mild</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Initial screen of AM2RLauncher</caption>
            <image type="source" width="822" height="759">https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/509717926807601182/999676114492461056/unknown.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
</component>
