<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022 AM2R Community Developers -->
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>io.github.am2rcommunitydevelopers.AM2RLauncher</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
    <name>AM2RLauncher</name>
    <developer_name>AM2R Community Developers</developer_name>
    <summary>A front-end for dealing with AM2R updates and mods</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Programm für die Handhabung mit AM2R-Updates und Mods</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Un front-end para organizar y controlar las actualizaciones y mods de AM2R</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="fr">Une interface pour intéragir avec les mods et MAJ de AM2R</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="it">Una front-end per gestire aggiornamenti e mod di AM2R</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt">Um front-end para gerenciar mods e atualizações do AM2R</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="ja">AM2Rの更新やMODを扱うためのフロントエンド</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="ru">Клиент для распоряжения обновлениями и модами для AM2R</summmary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh-Hans">一个负责管理 AM2R 的更新和 Mod 的前端</summmary>
    <categories>
        <category>Game</category>
    </categories>
    <description>
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake) is a fan-made remake of <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> in the style of <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em>.
            It was released in 2016 by DoctorM64 and his team, and very soon after, has received a DMCA letter from Nintendo.<br>
            A few years after, multiple members of the community managed to reverse engineer the game and published unofficial updates, 
            dubbed the AM2R-Community-Updates. Those fixed bugs and added new features like widescreen, added content planned by the original devs before 
            they were struck down, and ported it to other platforms.  
        </p>
        <p>
            The AM2RLauncher lets you conveniently play those Community-Updates, automatically receive updates, install AM2R mods and create 
            APKs to play on your phone.<br>
            No copyrighted files are shipped, you need to provide your own copy of AM2R_11!
        </p>
        <p>
            For further questions regarding AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">see this FAQ</a>.
            For further questions regarding the AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">see this Wiki</a>.
            For further communication, you can reach us on <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, 
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, or 
            <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub issues</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <!--TODO: russian-->
    <description xml:lang="de">
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake, Englisch für <em>ein weiteres Metroid 2 Remake</em>) ist ein von Fans entwickeltes Remake von 
            <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> im Stil von <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em>. Es wurde 2016 von DoctorM64 und seinem Team veröffentlicht, 
            erhielten aber kurz darauf rechtliche Klagen von Nintendo.<br>
            Ein paar Jahre später gelang es mehreren Mitgliedern der Gemeinde, das Spiel zu rekonstruieren und inoffizielle Updates zu veröffentlichen, 
            die AM2R-Community-Updates genannt werden. Diese behoben Fehler und fügten neue Funktionen wie Breitbild hinzu, 
            Inhalte die von den ursprünglichen Entwicklern geplant waren, und portierten das Spiel auf andere Betriebsysteme.
        </p>
        <p>
            Mit dem AM2RLauncher ist es möglich diese Community-Updates, als auch AM2R-Mods, bequem zu installieren, automatisch Updates zu erhalten, 
            und APKs für das Speielen auf dem Handy zu erstellen.<br>
            Es werden keine urheberrechtlich geschützten Dateien mitgeliefert, es muss eine eigene Kopie von AM2R_11 bereitgestellt werden!
        </p>
        <p>
            Für weitere Fragen zu AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">siehe dieses FAQ</a>.
            Für weitere Fragen bezüglich des AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">siehe dieses Wiki</a>.
            Für weitere Kommunikation sind wir auf <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, 
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, oder bei Problemen <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">auf GitHub</a> 
            zu erreichen.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="es"> 
        <p>
            AM2R (<em>Another Metroid 2 Remake</em>, que significa Otro Remake de Metroid 2) es un remake del juego para la Game Boy 
            <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> hecho por fans, utilizando un estilo similar al de <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em> para Game Boy Advance. 
            Lanzado originalmente en 2016 por DoctorM64 y su equipo, al poco tiempo recibió un aviso por parte de Nintendo, indicando que infringía 
            la Ley de Derechos de Autor de la Era Digital.<br>
            Unos años más tarde, un grupo de miembros pertenecientes a la comunidad lograron reproducir el funcionamiento del juego mediante ingeniería inversa 
            y consiguieron publicar actualizaciones no oficiales, apodadas <em>AM2R-Community-Updates</em> (Actualizaciones de la Comunidad de AM2R). 
            Estas actualizaciones arreglaron algunos bugs y añadieron características nuevas como la posibilidad de jugar en pantalla ancha, 
            así como otros contenidos extra que los desarrolladores originales tenían planeado lanzar antes de que les cerraran el proyecto. 
            También han conseguido portear el juego a otros sistemas.
        </p>
        <p>
            El programa AM2RLauncher te permite jugar de forma fácil a esas Actualizaciones de la Comunidad, recibir actualizaciones automáticas, 
            instalar mods para AM2R y crear archivos APK para poder jugar en tu móvil.<br>
            ¡No contiene ningún archivo protegido con copyright, deberás proporcionar tu propia copia de AM2R_11!
        </p>
        <p>
            Para más preguntas sobre AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">visita este FAQ</a>.
            Para más preguntas sobre AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">visita esta Wiki</a>.
            Para hablar con nosotros, puedes contactar mediante <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, 
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, o <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="fr">
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake) est un remake fait par des fans de <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> dans le style de <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em>. 
            Le jeu fut publié en 2016 par DoctorM64 et son équipe, et peu de temps après, reçut une lettre de DMCA de la part de Nintendo.<br>
            Quelques années après, plusieurs membre de la communauté réussirent à faire une rétro-ingénierie du jeu et publières des MAJ non-officielles, 
            appelées AM2R-Community-Updates. Elles corrigent des bugs et ajoutent de nouvelles fonctionalités comme un écran large, 
            et ajoutent du contenu prévu par les développeurs originaux avant la termination, et incluent des ports pour de nouvelles plateformes.  
        </p>
        <p>
            Le AM2RLauncher vous permet de jouer facilement à ces MAJ communautaires, recevoir les MAJ automatiquement, 
            installer les mods d&#39;AM2R et créer des APK pour jouer sur téléphone.<br>
            Aucun fichier sous copyright n&#39;est inclus, vous devez avoir votre propre archive de AM2R_11!
        </p>
        <p>
            Pour plus de questions sur AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">see this FAQ</a>.
            Pour plus de questions sur le AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">see this Wiki</a>.
            Pour plus d&#39;informations, vous pouvez nous joindre sur <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, 
            <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, ou <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub issues</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="it">
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake) è un remake creato dai fan di <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> nello stile di <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em>. 
            È stato rilasciato nel 2016 da DoctorM64 e il suo team, e poco dopo, ha ricevuto una lettera di DMCA da Nintendo.<br>
            Qualche anno dopo, molteplici membri della comunità sono riusciti ad estrapolare il gioco e pubblicare aggiornamenti non ufficiali, 
            rinominati Aggiornamenti della Comunità di AM2R.  Questi hanno sistemato i bug e aggiunto funzionalità come il widescreen, 
            aggiunto contenuti pianificati dagli sviluppatori originali prima di essere stati fermati, e portarli ad altre piattaforme. 
        </p>
        <p>L&#39;AM2RLauncher ti permette convenientemente di giocare a questi Aggiornamenti della Comunità, ricevere aggiornamenti automaticamente, 
        installare mod di AM2R e creare APK per giocare sul tuo cellulare. <br>
        Nessun file con copyright viene distribuito, avrai bisogno di fornire la tua copia di AM2R_11!</p>
        <p>
            Per ulteriori domande su AM2R <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">visita queste FAQ</a>.
            Per ulteriori domande su AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">visita questa Wiki</a>.
            Per ulteriori comunicazioni, puoi contattarci su <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, 
            o <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">problemi su GitHub</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="pt">
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake) é um remake de <em>Metroid II: Return of Samus</em> no estilo de <em>Metroid: Zero Mission</em> criado por fans. 
            Foi lançado em 2016 por DoctorM64 e sua equipe, porém foi retirado do ar após receber um aviso legal da Nintendo.<br>
            Alguns anos depois, múltiplos membros da comunidade conseguiram realizar a engenharia reversa do projeto e publicaram atualizações não oficiais, 
            chamadas de &quot;Atualizações da Comunidade do AM2R&quot;. Essas atualizações consertaram bugs, adicionaram novas funcionalidades como Widescreen, 
            adicionaram conteúdo planejado pelos desenvolvedores originais e portaram o jogo para outras plataformas.  
        </p>
        <p>
            O AM2RLauncher permite que você use as Atualizações da Comunidade com facilidade, receba atualizações automaticamente, instale mods e crie APKs para jogar no seu celular.  
        </p>
        <p>
            Para mais dúvidas sobre o AM2R, <a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">leia as perguntas frequentes.</a>.
            Para mais dúvidas sobre o AM2RLauncher <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">leia a Wiki</a>.
            Para outras dúvidas, você pode nos encontrar no <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, 
            ou <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">issues do GitHub</a>.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="ja">
        <p>
            AM2R (Another Metroid 2 Remake) は『Metroid II: Return of Samus』をメトロイドゼロミッションのスタイルでリメイクしたファンメイドの作品です。<br>
            DoctorM64と彼のチームによって2016年にリリースされたものの、すぐに任天堂から著作権侵害の警告を受けました。<br>
            数年後、コミュニティの複数のメンバーがゲームをリバースエンジニアリングすることに成功し、AM2R-Community-Updatesという非公式アップデートを公開しました。<br>
            その内容は、バグの修正、ワイドスクリーンのような新しい機能の追加、元の開発者が手を引く前に計画したコンテンツの追加、そして他のプラットフォームへの移植です。
        </p>
        <p>
            AM2RLauncherは、これらのCommunity-Updateを便利に扱うためのもので、自動アップデート、AM2R用のMODのインストール、スマートフォンでプレイするためのAPKの作成、といった機能があります。<br>
            なお著作権で保護されたファイルは含まれていないため、『AM2R_11.zip』ファイルを利用者自身が用意する必要があります。
        </p>
        <p>
            その他のAM2Rに関する疑問は<a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">こちらのFAQへ</a>.
            ほかAM2RLauncherに関する疑問は<a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">こちらのWikiへ</a>をご覧ください。
            さらなる情報をお求めなら<a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>, <a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a>, 
            または <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub issues</a> までご連絡ください。
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="zh-Hans">
        <p>
            AM2R（Another Metroid 2 Remake，意为另一个密特罗德2重制版）是以《密特罗德 零点任务》的游戏风格制作的《密特罗德II 萨姆斯的回归》的同人重制版。
            AM2R 最初由 DoctorM64 及其团队成员发布于 2016 年，并且在发布后不久收到了来自任天堂的 DMCA 邮件。<br>
            数年后，多位社区成员成功逆向工程了该游戏，并发布非官方更新版本，称之为“AM2R社区更新”（AM2R-Community-Updates）。
            社区更新在修复 Bug 的同时也添加了诸如宽屏显示的新功能，并且添加了原开发者在 AM2R 被叫停前所计划实现的内容，还将 AM2R 移植到了其他平台上。
        </p>
        <p>
            使用 AM2R 启动器（AM2RLauncher）可以方便地游玩社区更新版本，自动获取更新，安装 AM2R 的 Mod，还可以创建 APK 以安装在手机上进行游玩。<br>
            AM2R 启动器不会提供受版权保护的文件，需要用户自行提供 AM2R_11 的原始副本！
        </p>
        <p>
            有关 AM2R 的更多问题<a href="https://am2r-community-developers.github.io/DistributionCenter/faq.html">请见该 FAQ</a>。
            有关 AM2R 启动器的更多问题<a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki">请见该 Wiki</a>。
            如需与我们进一步交流，你可以在 <a href="https://discord.gg/nk7UYPbd5u">Discord</a>，<a href="https://matrix.to/#/#am2r-space:matrix.org">Matrix</a> 
            或者 <a href="https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues">GitHub 仓库的 Issues</a> 中联系我们。
        </p>
    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.am2rcommunitydevelopers.AM2RLauncher.desktop</launchable>
    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/issues</url>
    <url type="faq">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki/FAQ</url>
    <url type="help">https://github.com/AM2R-Community-Developers/AM2RLauncher/wiki</url>
    <releases>
        <release version="2.2.0" date="2022-01-07"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="language-humor">mild</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Initial screen of AM2RLauncher</caption>
            <image type="source" width="822" height="759">https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/509717926807601182/999676114492461056/unknown.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
</component>
